- You're talking about Leonard.
- No, no.
(Sheldon:)Shilly-Shally has red hair and
briefly served in the Mexican Navy.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, despite the fact
that he has a girlfriend...
(Sheldon:)...Shilly-Shally has been the recipient...
(Sheldon:)...of inappropriate workplace flirtations
from a young lady.
- It's your assistant Alex, isn't it?
- No.
No, it's Tondelaya della Ventimiglia.
What the hell is going on
with Leonard and Alex?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, who's talking about
Leonard and Alex?
(Penny:)Fine. Ricardo and Tondelaya.
(Sheldon:)It's not really about
Ricardo and Tondelaya.
(Sheldon:)It is really about her boss...
(Sheldon:)...who doesn't quite know how to handle
this situation and could use your advice...
(Sheldon:)...which is surprising, because
Dr. Einstein Von Brainstorm...
(Sheldon:)...he's usually pretty smart
about these things.
Ugh. I'm gonna kill her!
(Bernadette:)You've got nothing to worry about.
Leonard would never cheat on you.